{"results":[
  {"category":"Science & Nature","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"NURLANIN ADI NƏDİR?","correct_answer":"NURLAN","incorrect_answers":["TOFİQ","ƏLİ","ALPARSLAN"]},
{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"NURLAN HARADA YAŞAYIR?","correct_answer":"YASAMAL","incorrect_answers":["KAMÇATKA","MİAMİ","BAŞINDA"]},
{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"NURLAN NECƏ OĞLANDIR?","correct_answer":"YAXŞI","incorrect_answers":["BİLMİRƏM","PİS","OĞLAN?"]},
{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"NURLANIN ƏN YAXIN DOSTU KİMDİR?","correct_answer":"VASİF","incorrect_answers":["ƏRDOĞAN","PUTİN","Christian Bale"]},
{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"NURLAN HANSI KLUBUN FANATIDIR?","correct_answer":"LİVERPUL","incorrect_answers":["SABAH","KEŞLƏ","PUNİK"]},
{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"NURLANIN NEÇƏ GÖZÜ VAR?","correct_answer":"2","incorrect_answers":["3","1","0"]},
{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"NURLANIN PİS VƏRDİŞİ","correct_answer":"SİQORET","incorrect_answers":["31","PATI","QUMAR"]},
{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"NURLAN","correct_answer":"HƏ","incorrect_answers":["YOX","YOX","YOX"]},
{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"NURLANIN NEÇƏ GÜN MƏZUNİYYƏTƏ GƏLDİ?","correct_answer":"0","incorrect_answers":["10","365","5"]},
{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"NURLANIN NEÇƏ YAŞI VAR","correct_answer":"25","incorrect_answers":["31","11","51"]}]}
